[🎄 Extended Christmas Returns Are Here ! 🎁 Click here for details 📦 Order by 16th Dec for 🎄 Guaranteed Christmas Delivery! 🎅](https://veno-scorp.co.uk/pages/christmas-extended-policy)

 * All Gaming Pcs
    
    * SHOP BY BUDGET

* All Gaming Pcs

Item added to your cart
-----------------------

Check out

Continue shopping

Privacy & Security
==================

**Privacy**

Set out below is the Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) of Veno Scorp UK(“we”, “our”, “us” or the “Company”). Persons accessing our website("Site") or our products are referred to as “you.”

This Privacy Policy is a legally binding agreement between Veno Scorp(with offices located at Unit 174, Old Wellington Road, Lyntown Trading Estate,Manchester, M30 9FU, Greater Manchester, UK) and you as a user of our Site or our products.

This Privacy Policy describes the data we collect from you and how we use that data. Note that this may be updated at any time, so we suggest that you periodically check back here to get information about these updates.

●     PersonalInformation

We collect personal information from you. These are:

a) Unique identifiers, e.g., user name and password

b) Contact info such as name, email address, mailing address, bank account number and phone number

c) Device information, such as Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browsertype, an Internet service provider (ISP), the files viewed on our Site (e.g.,HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system and version, unique device identifiers, mobile network information, and information about the device's interaction with our services, date/time stamp, and clickstream data

d) Metadata, such as cookies; access time and date; referral/exit pages; click stream data; the website pages you visit; the time spent interacting on these pages or with certain parts of the website; and

We use this information based on your consent and to provide services including:

To identify and verify your identity.

To notify you of any upcoming events or activities or special offers you might be interested in.

To confirm you meet the minimum age requirements, when applicable, for all our events and promotions.

For display on our forum for other Site users to view.

To enable you to share information such as messages, videos, photos and screenshots to other forum users on our Site. (Please note that we are not responsible for the actions of other forum users when you share this info)

To aid the purchase of our products from the website.

For more comfortable delivery of any product, you may purchase from us.

For targeted and generic ads.

To analyse trends in the aggregate and administer the Site.

PLEASE NOTE: That we will not demand from you or collect sensitive personal information such as religious preferences, sexual orientation, gender, race, political opinions or ethnic origins, and we encourage you not to provide this information on any of our community forums.

●     How We Collect Your Data

We collect data and information in different ways, including what you provide, your interaction with our Site, and third-parties. Such information may include your name, email address, and telephone number, and so on. We collect this information in these ways:

Information You Give Us - You provide us with certain information in the following ways:

Filling in forms on our website. This includes information provided when signing up, paying for our products, posting material or requesting further services.

When you report a problem with our service or have a question about our service.

If you contact us, please record and copy your letter (including your email address).

Details of your transactions through our services and order fulfilment.

Your search query on our website or through our services. If you do not provide us with personal data, your ability to use certain aspects of our products and services may be restricted.

●     Who We Share Your Data To?

We will not share your data with anyone except:

With Your Consent: We may share your data for any lawful purpose you have expressly consented to or directed.

With Our Business Partners and Vendors: These are companies that provide services to help us with our business activities, such as email service providers, customerservice or event management contractors.

We would only share the information needed to enable them to perform the required job description.

**Compliance with The Law:** we may release your data in the following situations:

Comply with any court order, law or legal process, including responding to any government or regulatory request.

In order to implement any agreement, we may reach to you.

To protect the safety, rights, property of us, other customers or any other person.

To prevent activities that we unilaterally believe may become illegal, unethical, or actionable according to the law.

To protect our copyrights or intellectual property.

●     Retaining of your Data

We will retain any information you provide us in the course of your using our Site. We will keep your information for a while consistent with the original reason that the information was collected or for the period needed for us to pursue our legitimate business interests, comply with our legal obligations, resolve any complaints or disputes you may have, and enforce our agreements.

●     Public Disclosure

Our Site has publicly accessible community forums to enable users to share gaming tips and information in the form of text, photos, screenshots or videos. Any information you provide in these forums can be read, collected, and used by others who visit them. When you share this information, we are not responsible for other forum users' actions, so we encourage you to keep this in mind.

●     Link to other websites

This website may contain links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us. We will not take responsibility for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage you to pay attention to when you leave our website and read each website's privacy policy that you click on that collects personal information. This privacy policy only applies to information contained on this website.

●     children

We would not intentionally collect or solicit information from anyone under the age of 13 (under 16 in the European Union) or intentionally allow such persons to register. If you are under 13 (age 16 in the EU), please do not register on the Site. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under such minimum age in any circumstances, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We encourage children to ask permission from their parents before posting any personal information online or providing this information on any websites.

**Security**

We consider the security of your personal information to be of paramount importance to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as login credentials), the information and transmission are encrypted through secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We also employ other administrative, physical, and electronic measures to protect your information from unauthorized access, such as firewalls and transport layer security (TLS) or hypertext transfer protocol secure (HTTPS) to protect your data.

However, we cannot guarantee a hundred per cent the security of our databases, nor guarantee fully that any information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet or other network .Any information you transmit to us, you do at your own risk.

Please ensure not to share your passwords with anyone. We will disclose any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored data as is legally required.

**Opting Out**

You may opt-out of receiving our newsletters or marketing emails by clicking unsubscribe in any email we send to you.

You might also withdraw your consent at any time for any processing of your personal information we do base on the consent you have provided to us.

Note, however, that once you have opted out by withdrawing your consent, you may not be able to access and use our services and our products or parts of our services and our products.

**Changes**

We will make periodic changes to this Privacy Policy as time goes on. We encourage you to periodically review it to be sure you are familiar with the most current version.

We may (please note that this is not guaranteed) notify you (through the email you give us) when we make any significant changes to our Privacy Policy that affect the use of any data we collect. Still, you should regularly checkback here to be fully aware of any changes.

**Mobile Terms of Service**

NH TRADING NW LIMITED

Last updated: March 4, 2024

The NH TRADING NW LIMITED mobile message service (the "Service") is operated by NH TRADING NW LIMITED (“NH TRADING NW LIMITED”, “we”, or “us”). Your use of the Service constitutes your agreement to these terms and conditions (“Mobile Terms”). We may modify or cancel the Service or any of its features without notice. To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may also modify these Mobile Terms at any time and your continued use of the Service following the effective date of any such changes shall constitute your acceptance of such changes.

By consenting to NH TRADING NW LIMITED’s SMS/text messaging service, you agree to receive recurring SMS/text messages from and on behalf of NH TRADING NW LIMITED through your wireless provider to the mobile number you provided, even if your mobile number is registered on any state or federal Do Not Call list. Text messages may be sent using an automatic telephone dialing system or other technology. Service-related messages may include updates, alerts, and information (e.g., order updates, account alerts, etc.). Promotional messages may include promotions, specials, and other marketing offers (e.g., cart reminders).

You understand that you do not have to sign up for this program in order to make any purchases, and your consent is not a condition of any purchase with NH TRADING NW LIMITED. Your participation in this program is completely voluntary.

We do not charge for the Service, but you are responsible for all charges and fees associated with text messaging imposed by your wireless provider. Message frequency varies. Message and data rates may apply. Check your mobile plan and contact your wireless provider for details. You are solely responsible for all charges related to SMS/text messages, including charges from your wireless provider.

You may opt-out of the Service at any time. Text the single keyword command STOP to Veno Scorp or click the unsubscribe link (where available) in any text message to cancel. You'll receive a one-time opt-out confirmation text message. No further messages will be sent to your mobile device, unless initiated by you. If you have subscribed to other NH TRADING NW LIMITED mobile message programs and wish to cancel, except where applicable law requires otherwise, you will need to opt out separately from those programs by following the instructions provided in their respective mobile terms.

For Service support or assistance, text HELP to Veno Scorp or email [support@veno-scorp.co.uk](mailto:support@veno-scorp.co.uk "mailto:support@veno-scorp.co.uk")

We may change any short code or telephone number we use to operate the Service at any time and will notify you of these changes. You acknowledge that any messages, including any STOP or HELP requests, you send to a short code or telephone number we have changed may not be received and we will not be responsible for honoring requests made in such messages.

The wireless carriers supported by the Service are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages. You agree to provide us with a valid mobile number. If you get a new mobile number, you will need to sign up for the program with your new number.

To the extent permitted by applicable law, you agree that we will not be liable for failed, delayed, or misdirected delivery of any information sent through the Service, any errors in such information, and/or any action you may or may not take in reliance on the information or Service.

We respect your right to privacy. To see how we collect and use your personal information, please see our Privacy Notice.

Here is a link but we need to ensure right email is there [support@veno-scorp.co.uk](mailto:support@veno-scorp.co.uk "mailto:support@veno-scorp.co.uk")

Welcome to Veno Scorp one of the UK'S Largest gaming pc builders.

Products

Your Account

Need Help?

Quick Links

Contact & Support

Email: support@veno-scorp.co.uk

Telephone: 0161 241 8412

Copyright © 2020 Veno Scorp (NH Trading Nw Limited), Unit 174-176 Old Wellington Rd, M30 9FU, Company Re: 09747874

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Opens in a new window.

### Build Your Dream Machine

Do you need help building your Dream Pc? Fill out the details below and we will call you shortly.

×

Name \* 

Email \* 

Phone number \* 

Budget \* 

Send
